♫ Magic stack of old cards ♫
♫ From the Fortune Teller, ♫
♫ Eight clones summoned to this world, ♫
♫ And every one of them: ♫
♫ A different look, ♫
♫ A different hook, ♫
♫ And different outlook ♫
♫ On what’s good ♫
♫ And who’s the king, and who’s the jack, ♫
♫ Wish you good luck on keeping track! ♫
♫ What could possibly go wrong? ♫
♫  EVERYTHING WENT WRONG! ♫
I WILL LITERALLY KILL YOU, CHARLIE!
THAT’S A FELONY, RICCARDO!
What’s all that noise
Where is it?..
There’s no foooood!
Peppers, cabbage, eggplant.
There’s absolutely nothing to eat!
Do you not like your greens, Waru?
I do, but the other kind.
Why don’t we order something in?
That’s a great idea!
Fёdor didn’t like us spending money on takeaway.
Are you suggesting we finish the pasta?
Fine, you won.
And this needs to be destroyed.
Eugh…
What do we order?
How about pizza?
I want suuuushi!
But sushi don’t want you!
You can do better than that.
It’s all because I’m hungry!
This monster needs protein! Carbs!
Uh…! What else is there? Help me out, Kuromaku!
Polyunsaturated fats, amino acids…
Shut it, Kuromaku!
What did you say?
You shut it, you!
This isn’t my forte
yeah!
you green little…
Come on, put ‘em up!
Ha!
Two down! More for us…
Come on! High five!
You stuck a push pin to your hand.
You were way more fun without the glasses!...
Dante!
Can I come with?
So… Are you taking a walk?
Yes, it’s a delightful evening.
hat’s true…uhhh?
What happened to: “Evening strolls pave the way - for your gland's health every day”?
Do you mind if we stop over somewhere?
Who wants what?
I want more meat!
I want more cheese!
I want MORE!
I want.
I.
Okay, they have something new! Pizza…
with pears?
Ew! What kind of pervert came up with that?!
That’s sickening…
Sraephtiw???
How about Hawaiian?
Oh, pineapples! Pineapples!
It has chicken in it.
THE WORLD HAS GONE MAD!
I worked it out!
“Sraephtiw” is “with pears” backwards.
Agh.
Pepperoni’s on its way!
Normally I feel anxious at night, but today I feel calm…
The first snow!
Looks like winter came early.
I'm only interested in the bent Criminal Artists, let's go!
Finally!
I’ll get it!
We don’t have enough stools
Where are they?
On the balcony.
I’ll go get them.
Wait…
We usually eat in front of the TV… On the sofa…
Waru, no Waru!…
I’m taking your slice!
You can have it, just let me back in!
You know too much!
Gabriel! Open the door!
Spade!
Spade, open the door!
He wrote us into his will.
Pah! Nice.
Oh, Fedya! You’re back early!
Oh, right…  you’re a courier… What a coincidence, isn’t it?
Seriously?
I work evenings just so you could spend my money on takeaway?
But we’re bad at cooking!
Well, you should learn!
Whatever, we’ll talk when I get back!
Wait!
Here’s your tip!
But I don’t have… Romeo?
Fedya, can I borrow some?
Alright…
Thank you!
Here are my tips! Bye!
Okay guys, pizza’s here! OUCH!-
Have you ever noticed that the stars and snowflakes are similar?
Even though they’re completely different.
Snowflakes are so small and fragile.
And the stars are so big and bright.
But in our eyes they acquire common features and merge into one.
It’s as if the stars fall from the sky so that everyone in the world gets a wish…
Hmm…
should we make a wish?
Can’t see why not…
Hey! Why are you two loitering?!
This is a kids’ playground.
All they do is break and break… they already broke them once…
Huh?
You’ve had enough!
Hey! What?
You’ve already had two slices!
And I had the smallest one!
That’s too easy!
Either way, I’m still hungry!
Why don’t you finish it then?
I don’t like the crust…
I call dibs!
Ouch!
Friends!
It’s not right to fight over a slice of pizza…
Let’s do the right thing and save it for the other guys when they come back!
Hey, what the?!
I SAID LET’S DO THE RIGHT THING!
Looks like they’ll only let me in after I get frostbite…
I have to move to stay alive.
I DON’T need to move to stay alive…
AHHHH!
Kuromaku?! Where did you come from?!
Obviously from up there.
The higher you climb, the harder you fall.
This again…
Maybe… we could walk some more?
Evening strolls pave the way - for your gland's health every day.
Wait… that’s…
In this case, I have to agree.
Dante was talking to me today without using a single quote! Imagine that!
Brolly, I’m only just starting to develop an imagination.
Why did my courier rating drop after I delivered to you?!
I gave you two stars.
Seriously?!
Spade… Why?
The pizza was cold, he ate one of the slices, and…
he’s Fёdor.
Yeah. Fair enough.
Yeah.
What? I’m honest.
Gabriel?!
Me?
Are you out for a walk? I’ll get my jacket!
Oh!
I forgot my mittens!
Shall we?
What’s going on with this tree?!
It’s the stars…